Guide to the Western Connecticut State University Photographs and Miscellanea RG 8
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series III: Clippings, 55202
  - 2003, 55266
    - October 2003 Clippings (copies), 55274 (Box clippings_6, Folder 17)
      Oct 5, 2003: Philharmonia Virtuosi will perform at Ives Concert Hall; Oct 8: 2003: Board questions rush to find location for Magnet School; Oct 20, 2003: WestConn upgrades await state funds; Oct 30, 2003: Debate Club started by Dr. Christopher Kukk
    - October 2003 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55273 (Box clippings_6, Folder 18)
      Oct 2-21, 2003: Continued coverage of WCSU's teams; Oct 22, 2003: WestConn to induct fourth class into Athletic Hall of Fame.
    - October 2003 Video Monitoring Services, 55272 (Box clippings_6, Folder 19)
      WCSU October/November Media Coverage.
    - November 2003 Clippings (originals), 55271 (Box clippings_6, Folder 20-21)
      Nov 1-30, 2003: WCSU media coverage; Nov 2, 2003: Isabelle Farrington wins award; Nov 2, 2003: Biology prof. Mitch Wagener studying the eclogy of stone walls in N.E.; Nov 2,6,13, 2003: Kiss Me, Kate by the Communications and Theatre Arts Department; Nov 12, 2003: State tuition to increase again; Nov 20, 2003: Time capsule sealed; Nov 21, 2003: WCSU enrollment grows.
    - November 2003 Clippings (copies), 55270 (Box clippings_6, Folder 22)
      Nov 2,6, 13, 2003: Kiss Me Kate production of the Communications and Theatre Arts Department; Nov 2, 2003; State tuition to increase; Nov 2, 2003: Isabelle Farrington wins award for giving; Nov 2, 2003: Mitch Wagener, biology prof. at WCSU, studying the ecology of stone walls in New England; Nov 7, 2003: Lunar eclipse of the moon.
    - November 2003 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55269 (Box clippings_6, Folder 23)
      Nov 9, 2003: Men's soccer team wins LEC title; Nov 10, 2003: Women's volleyball wins 5th straight title; Nov 11, 2003: Men's and women's soccer teams set for NCAA tournaments; nov.15, 2003: Women volleyball team eliminated from NCAA Div. III; Nov 16, 2003: Men's soccer team eliminated; Nov 16, 2003: Men's soccer team eliminated; Nov 24, 2003: Men's basketball team win Vassar Men's Basketball Invitational.
    - December 2003 Clippings (originals), 55268 (Box clippings_6, Folder 24)
      Dec 7, 2003: Deems Taylor biography by Jim Pegolotti published; Dec 7, 2003: Tuition average increase 12.5%; Dec 14, 2003: Eleanor Feeley Lawry, WASP spent war ferrying trainer planes; and, Connie Nappier, Jr. member of Tuskegee Airmen (partial article); Dec 26, 2003: A Century Ago: State unveils plans for DNS.
    - December 2003 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55267 (Box clippings_6, Folder 25)
      Men's and women's basketball coverage.
    - Digest (4 issues), Jan 2003 - May 2003; 55692 (Box Clippings Digest 1, Item 21-24)
      Includes Jan, Mar, Apr, and May.
      January 2003 Digest: Dec 5: Wayne Shepperd, president and publisher of the News-Times received WestConn Society Community Service Award; Dec 6: News-Times A Century Ago: Danbury, Waterbury vie for state normal school; Dec 8, 2002: State approves land for performing arts center in Danbury; Dec 13: The Shelter of the Cross house in Danbury; Dec 20: A Century Ago: Board makes push for Normal School in Danbury; Dec 22: Curriculum doctorate is new WestConn offering by Koryeo Anim-Wright.
      March 2003 Digest: Dec 18, 2002: Morganti Group Spotlight Story; Jan 17: Danbury area graffiti inspires documentary; Jan 20: Bethel High School seniors take courses at WCSU; Jan. 22-3: Tom Crucitti, Bernie Reidy, John Smoliga, Barbara Warner Obeda, and Dave McKane receive Centennial Award for Excellence from Dr. Dallas K. Beal; Jan 26: Cake celebration kicks off final semester of centennial by Koryeo Anim-Wright.
      Sports: Feb 7: Women's basketball Tory Anderton interviewed.
      April 2003 Digest: Mar 10: V-Day, Until The Violence Stops event; Mar 13: Author Mark Hetsgaard discusses his book "Earth Odyssey;" Mar 17: David Machell and bagpipes.
      May 2003 Digest: Mar 13: The Imaginary Invalid, a farce by Moliere, production by the Communications and Theater Arts Department; Mar 14: Peter Whitney, photographer, interview; Mar 20: WCSU's capital campaign; Mar 21: Barbara Obeda's activism recalled; Mar 21; Anti-war protest; Mar 21: James Scrimgeour, community poet; Mar 26: Lake authority hires Larry Mariscano; Mar 26: Geologist John Pawloski; Mar 28: "Ladies of City Point" Civil War's Quiet Heroines by Jeanne Christie; Mar 29: WestConn receives $840,000 grant for new art center; Apr 8: City loses bid for mercury study money; Apr 8: State grant to help town buy Henderson farmland for open space; Apr 9: Nancy White Cassidy, illustrator, interview; Apr 9: Using plants to clear toxic mercury from soil; Apr 10: WestConn adds a gerontology program; Apr 20: H.M.S. Pinafore production reviewed by James Pegolotti; Apr 21: Dan Goble profiled.
  - 2004, 55239
    - January 2004 Clippings (originals), 55265 (Box clippings_6, Folder 26)
      Jan 9, 2004: Deems Taylor book signing; Jan 21, 2004: SCSU to hire female president.
    - January 2004 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55264 (Box clippings_6, Folder 27)
      Jan 17, 25, 2004: WestConn ice hocky; Jan 1-25, 2004: Men/women basketball.
    - February 2004 Clippings (originals), 55263 (Box clippings_6, Folder 28)
      Feb 4-20, 2004: Frederic Chiu, pianist, performs at WestConn; Feb 18, 2004: Campus Expenses in Conn. Ranked highest in nation; Feb 10, 2004: Wellesley Inn houses WestConn overflow of students.
    - February 2004 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55262 (Box clippings_6, Folder 29)
      Feb 25, 2004: WestConn men win Little East opener.
    - March 2004 Clippings (originals), 55261 (Box clippings_6, Folder 30)
      Mar 18, 2004: Branson Ultrasonics pledge $100,000 to WCSU; Mar 20, 2004: CCSU president Judd retires after scandal; Mar 20, 2004: WestConn raises $4.1 million, Boehring cited (first major fund raising); Mar 30, 2004: State pulls matching funds for colleges.
    - March 2004 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55260 (Box clippings_6, Folder 31)
      Mar 7-8, 2004: WCSU reaches ECAC final (men's basketball); Mar 11, 2004: Women's Lacross opening season.
    - April 2004 Clippings (originals), 55259 (Box clippings_6, Folder 32)
      Apr 1, 2004: WCSU unveils plans for $65M arts center; Apr 5, 2004: Women's book spotlights local statues; Apr 5, 2004: WCSU debate team defeats big league schools.
    - April 2004 Clippings (copies), 55258 (Box clippings_6, Folder 33)
      Apr 2, 30, 2004: Mia Farrow to speak at WestConn; Apr 7,16,23, 2004: Evening of jazz with Sherry Winston; Sights & Sounds 2004 at the Silo; The Deans' Lectures at WCSU: Terror & Democracy by Todd Brewster; Apr 23, 2004: "Street Scene" production by the WCSU's Opera Ensemble; Apr 26, 2004: Third annual WestConn AniFest; Apr 30, 2004: WestConn show "Freedom Live 2004" going to Iraq.
    - April 2004 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55257 (Box clippings_6, Folder 34)
      Apr 1-28, 2004: Men's and women's sports on win streak; Apr 29, 2004: WCSU fall in conference lacrosse playoff.
    - May 2004 Clippings (originals), 55256 (Box clippings_6, Folder 35-39)
      May 1, 20204: WestConn shortens list of president candidates; May 7, 2004: WestConn president candidate criticized; May 8, 2004: Freshmen get name changed to "first year students;" 'May 9, 2004: "In the Cards" by Dr. Mel Goldstein; May 15, 2004: WCSU's Dance Team "Forces of Dance;" May 23, 2004: Jane Goodall speaks at WCSU about war and the environment; May 26, 28, 2004: Candlewood Lake the topic at four-week lecture series; May 27, 2004: Hord Foundation sets up math academy.
    - May 2004 Clippings (copies), 55255 (Box clippings_6, Folder 40)
      May 1, 2004: Transgenic trees may remove mercury from soil; May 3, 2004: WestConn students produce variety show "Freedom Live 2004" for troops; May 7, 2004: WCSU Waterbury branch; May 8, 2004: Freshmen get name change; May 15, 2004: WCSU Dance Team; May 23, 2004: Jane Goodall on war and environment; May 28, 2004: Candlewood Lake, past present and future lecture series.
    - May 2004 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55254 (Box clippings_6, Folder 41)
      May 2, 2004: Women's softball team wins Little East title; May 9, 2004: Women fall short in New England Div. III regionals.
    - June 2004 Clippings (originals), 55253 (Box clippings_7, Folder 1)
      Jun 3, 2004: WestConn picks James Smotter as president; Jun 9, 2004: Land trust honors Skitch and Ruth Henderson; Jun 11, 2004: NSA certifies WestConn courses; Jun 14, 2004: Prof.Oluwole Owoye tell story of Nigerian odyssey; Jun 16, 2004: WestConn students unearth Indian artifacts along the Housatonic River; Jun 16, 2004: WestConn students unearth Indian artifacts along the Housatonic River; Jun 16, 2004: WestConn students unearth Indian artifacts along the Housatonic River; Jun 23, 2004: Danbury Hospital and WestConn reach teaching deal.
    - June 2004 Clippings (copies), 55252 (Box clippings_7, Folder 2)
      Jun 5, 2004: CSU might trim tuition increase; Jun 8, 2004: WestConn and local high schools team up to prepare students for college; Jun 11, 2004: Diverse lineup for Ives Concert Park; Jun 11, 2004; Candlewood Lake Lecture on Jun 17; Jun 15, 2004: New WestConn president goes "west;" Jun 15, 2004: Trustees slash tuition hike; Jun 16, 2004: New plans alter magnet school; Jun 26, 2004: Crews take time to restore forgotten cemetery.
    - June 2004 Burrelle's report, 55251 (Box clippings_7, Folder 3)
      Jun 14-22: Burrelle's eClips
    - July 2004 Clippings (originals), 55250 (Box clippings_7, Folder 4)
      July.15, 2004: Gravestone Studies conference held at WCSU; Jul 26, 2004: Great grandaughter of John Perkins, first principal of DNS, donates portraits to WCSU archives; Jul 31, 2004: Seventh Ave. to become Dr. James Roach Avenue.
    - August 2004 Clippings (originals), 55249 (Box clippings_7, Folder 5)
      Aug 28, 2004: Skitch Henderson Exhibit opens at the Silo; Aug 28, 2004: Gertrude E. Braun obituary.
    - August 2004 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55248 (Box clippings_7, Folder 6)
      Aug 3, 2004: WestConn teams gets four new logos; Aug 10, 2004: Peter Schachter becomes new men's soccer coach.
    - September 2004 Clippings (originals), 55247 (Box clippings_7, Folder 7)
      Sep 3, 2004: A Century Ago: Normal School opens with 37 students enrolled; Sep 4-5,7,8,12,17, 2004: College student stabbed; Sep 7, 2004: Darla and Ben Shaw attend Hobo Convention; Sep 14, 2004: WestConn nursing program to ease state shortage; Sep 16, 2004: Students to debate energy issues; Sep 17, 2004: WestConn increases campus security.
    - September 2004 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55246 (Box clippings_7, Folder 8)
      Men's football and soccer; women's soccer.
    - October 2004 Clippings (originals), 55245 (Box clippings_7, Folder 9-10)
      Oct 3, 2004: Victim recalls WestConn stabbing; Oct 7, 2004: City, WestConn to hold forum on toxic cleanup; Oct 10, 2004: City turns to trees to purge mercury; Oct 14,28, 2004: Appellate Court to hear three cases in Danbury; Oct 18, 2004: WestConn crime on decrease; Oct 19, 2004: Mary (Marmorstein) Young obituary; Oct 23,26, 2004: New dorm on westside campus; Oct 24, 2004: Southford Falls dig unearths site's industrial past.
    - October 2004 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55244 (Box clippings_7, Folder 11)
      Oct 1-31, 2004: Teams begin new season with wins and losses.
    - November 2004 Clippings (originals), 55243 (Box clippings_7, Folder 12)
      Nov 1,4, 2004: The Mystery of Edwin Drood by the Communications and Theatrer Arts Department; Nov 3, 2004: Dr. Thomas Michael Butterworth obituary; Nov 9, 2004: Burton Peretti bound for Germany; Nov 11, 2004: Non-trad life at WCSU; Nov 18, 2004: Ronald J. Chriss, chemistry professor, obituary; Nov 21, 2004: Abandoned houses on Osborne Street; Nov 18, 2004: Faculty debate stem cell use; Nov 24, 2004: Hendersons receive award for service to community.
    - November 2004 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55242 (Box clippings_7, Folder 13)
      Nov 21, 2004: WCSU men's basketball coach Bob Campell celebrates his 400th win; Nov 21, 2004: Women's soccer wins ECAC championship; Nov 27, 2004: WestConn men's team win northeast rugby championship.
    - December 2004 Clippings (originals), 55241 (Box clippings_7, Folder 14)
      Dec 10, 2004: Maria Silwa to discuss slavery in Africa; Dec 14, 2004: State Oks $2M for Westconn upgrades; WCSU to purchase Holy Trinity Orthodox Church; Dec 24, 2004: Jim Pegolotti wins ASCAP award for Deems Taylor: A Biography
    - December 2004 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55240 (Box clippings_7, Folder 15)
      Dec 1-31, 2004: Men's and women's basketball.
    - Digest (7 issues), Apr 2004 - Dec 2004; 55693 (Box Clippings Digest 2, Item 25-31)
      Includes Apr-Jul, and Oct-Dec.
      April 2004 Digest: Feb 6: Pianist Frederic Chiu to perform Feb 10; Feb 18: Advocate for Afghani Women's Rights to Seak Feb 19; Feb 22:Girls taking interest in science; Feb 22: Planets and stars; Feb 24: Presidential hopeful Ralph Nader; Mar 3: WestConn nears fund-raising goal; Mar 5 "Twelfth Night" a hippie delight.
      Mar 2004 Digest: Mar 15: WestConn wins $250,000 grant tocombat drug, alcohol abuse; Mar 20: WestConn raises $4.1 million; Mar 21: WestConn events target abuse; Mar 21: WestConn President James Roach has lifelong passion for baseball continues; Mar 24: CPTV program to feature trio of region's most active senior volunteers (Jean Kreizinger, Edwin Rosenberg, Jim Pegolotti; Mar 25: Jan Dow and daughter Shannon Dow have written "The Moor Lark" a play about them and their family; Mar 28: Hispanic organizations active at WestConn; Apr 1: WestConn surpasses goal, raises more than $4 million; Apr 1: WestConn and $65M arts center; Apr 5: Women's book spotlights local statues; Apr 5: Young WestConn debate team defeats big league schools; Apr 7: Henderson farm land dedicated as open space; Apr 9: "Street Scene" coming to Danbury; Apr 12: Local authors to speak at AAUW rund-raiser (James Pegolotti, Karen Kendall, Lauren Baritz-Longsted); Apr 18: WestConn Echo issue held for questionable content.
      Sports: Mar 4: Michele Tarzia inducted into WCSU Hall of Fame; Apr 3: Men's baseball; Apr 16: Joe Kegler returns to WestConn.
      June 2004 Digest: Mar 19: Branson Ultrasonics donates $100,000; Mar 19: United Way to honor Tony Pajk and Lynn Tabsorak; Apr 2,7,23: "Street Scene" by WCSU Opera Ensemble; Apr 2,9,30: Mia Farrow to speak at WestConn; Apr 15: Todd Brewster, newsman, lectures on terrorism and Constitution; Apr 25: WestConn's Criminology Club to focus on victim; Apr 26: Third annual WestConn AniFest; Apr 30: Pianist Orlie Shaham, pianist, review by Howard Tuvelle; Apr 30, May 3: WestConn show "Freedom Live 2004" to go to Iraq; May 2: Danbury Museum to host spring rail fair; May 7,13: Gerard Robilotti and Gary Hawley received WCSU's President's Medal; May 7: WCSU Waterbury branch; May 8: Freshmen get name change to "first year students;" May 15: WCSU Dance Team celebrates 10-year anniversary; May 23: Jane Goodall speaks about war and the environment.
      July 2004 Digest: May 26, 28: June Lecture Series to focus on Candlewood Lake's Past, Present and Future; May 27: Hord Foundation sets up math academy; Jun 3,15: WestConn's new president, James Schmotter; Laurie Weinstein and students unearth Indian artifacts; Jun 17: Henry Barnard Award to Lillian McKee and Ilana Ofgang; Jun 17: Charles Mullaney and Northern Ireland; Danbury Hospital and WestConn reach teaching agreement; Jun 26: Ed Siergiej and restoration of forgotten cemeteries.
      October 2004 Digest:Jun 30: WestConn to split Communications, Theatre Art Departments; Haas Library receives first national honor; Jul 5: Herb Janick and Danbury Hatter's Biographical Project; Jul 24: WestConn arts building a priorty; Jul 26: Elizabeth Perkins MacGregor, great grandaughter of John Perkins, donates photos of Perkins to Haas Library;Jul 31: Seventh Avenue becomes Dr. James Roach Avenue; Aug 13: James W. Schmotter begins presidency
      Sports: Men's soccer and football; Aug 3: WestConn teams get new logo; Aug 18: Men's soccer coach Wayne Mones; Sep 1: Women's soccer look to capture LEC title; Sep 3: Men's football Nick Frayer.
      November 2004 Digest: Sep 17: Waterbury branch gets approval for two degrees; James Schmotter interview; Oct 1: WestConn plans series of events to inform voters; Sep 24: Holocaust survivor David Faber to share his story; Sep 30: Barbara Manners to host Project Vote Smart; Oct 1: WestConn named to Homeland Security/Defense Education Consortium; Oct 1: David Faber and holocaust; Oct 10: Trees used to clean up mercury in Danbury brownfields; Oct 17: Dr. Russell Fryer scholarship honors late son, Kenneth Fryer.
      December 2004 Digest: Oct 20: Gov Rell to attend ribbon cutting for new residence's hall; Oct 22,28,31, Nov 3,5: "The Mystery of Edwin Drood" interactive mystery; Oct 29: WestConn plays host to Appellate Court; Nov 3: Music Prof Wesley Ball teaches through critical listening;Nov 5: Dr. Robert H. Frank, economist, to lecture at WestConn; Nov 6: Japanese tea ceremony; Nov 10: Prof Abubaker Saad on Yasser Arafat.
      Sports: Nov 21: Women's soccer wins ECAC championship; Nov 21: Men's basketball coach earns 400th win; Nov 27: WCSU's Rugy Team are Northeast champions.
  - 2005, 55215
    - January 2005 Clippings (originals), 55238 (Box clippings_7, Folder 16)
      Jan 24, 2005: Skitch Henderson to receive Smithson Bicentennial Medal; Jan 21, 2005: Danbury gives approval for school on Osborne Street; Jan 27, 2005: WestConn students to perform Psycho Beach Party comedy.
    - January 2005 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55237 (Box clippings_7, Folder 17)
      Jan 6, 2005: Richard Myers, WestConn volleyball program; Jan 5-30, 2005: Brice Assie, men's basketball.
    - February 2005 Clippings (originals), 55236 (Box clippings_7, Folder 18)
      Feb 5, 2005: "SimMan" robot, a $28,000 robot patient in nursing program; Feb 13, 2005: Tuition freeze proposal; Feb 16, 2005: Arts Center in Rell budget; Feb 17, 2005: James Schmotter assembles new team; Feb 20, 2005; WestConn honors members of Black Student Alliance.
    - February 2005 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55235 (Box clippings_7, Folder 19)
      Feb 17, 2005: Brice Assie, men's basketball; Feb 22, 2005: WestConn hockey; Feb 27, 2005: Colonials win LEC title.
    - March 2005 Clippings (originals), 55234 (Box clippings_7, Folder 20)
      Mar 3-4, 2005: The Distance From Here, a drama by playwright Neil LaBute; Mar 3, 2005: Prof. Tom Philbrick expert in Latin American river weeds finds new species; Mar 4, 2005: A Century Ago "Normal School building takes shape on White Street;" Mar 14, 2005: Work to begin on Magnet School, WestConn project; Mar 18, 2005: WestConn students, staff sacrifice hair for charity; Mar 20, 2005: Prof.Theodora Pinou leads study of turtles.
    - March 2005 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55233 (Box clippings_7, Folder 21)
      Mar 2, 2005: Brice Assie WestConn's player of the year; Mar 6, 2005: WestConn men's basketball ends season with loss.
    - April 2005 Clippings (originals), 55232 (Box clippings_7, Folder 22)
      Apr 11, 2005: David Beardsley's historic postcard exhibit; Apr 15, 2005: Jim Pegolotti review: Jupiter Symphony Chamber Players; Apr 15-16, 2005: Inauguration of James Schmotter; Apr 21,25, 2005: Will Michael, WCSU senior, wins grant for Old Nature Quarry documentary.
    - April 2005 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55231 (Box clippings_7, Folder 23)
      Apr 3, 2005: Men's lacrosse team records first-ever victory in a Little East Conference game; Apr 14, 2005: Foootball players clean up YMCA Day Camp; Apr 24, 2004: Dennis Skarda leads men's lacrosse to victory; Women's lacrosse; Men's baseball and tennis teams.
    - May 2005 Clippings (originals), 55230 (Box clippings_7, Folder 24)
      May 5, 2005: Theodora Pinou leads turtle research on Crete; May 6, 2005: Ellen Rosenberg's book Success, Fame, Happiness, Riches about Anna Rosenberg; May 6, 2005: Jim Pegolotti review: "WestConn concert blends three eras;" May 6,9-10, 2005: Jane Goodall Roots and Shoots; May 13, 2005: WestConn planning new parking area; May 13, 2005: Blue Window by the Communications and Theatre Arts Department; May 15, 2005: Jane Goodall discusses world's diminishing fresh water supply; May 20, 2005: Jim Pegolotti review: Horn concerto at Ives Concert Hall; May 25, 2005: WestConn in line for $3.7M grant; May 27, 2005: Filipino dancers to perform at WestConn.
    - May 2005 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55229 (Box clippings_7, Folder 25)
      May 12, 2005: Powder puff rugby game at WestConn; May 12, 2005: Women's softball win ECAC; May 15, 2005: Men's baseball team loses in LEC final.
    - June 2005 Clippings (originals), 55228 (Box clippings_7, Folder 26)
      Jun 2, 2005: Filipino dancers to perform at WCSU; Jun 4, 2005: Laurie Weinstein and WestConn students to join dig in Colorado.
    - July 2005 Clippings (originals), 55227 (Box clippings_7, Folder 27)
      Jul 3, 2005: Symphony concert of Ives music; Leonard Bernstein and protégé Michael Tilson Thomas; Jul 15, 2005: CSUS Cibes announces retirement; Jul 24, 2005: The Lady and the Panda by Vicki Constantine Croke; Jul 27,29, 2005: John Tamas, WCSU student obituary.
    - July 2005 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55226 (Box clippings_7, Folder 28)
      Jul 27, 2005: Jason Ouellet, new men's lacrosse coach; Jul 3,2005: Defensive tackle Lou Falco.
    - August 2005 Clippings (originals), 55225 (Box clippings_7, Folder 29)
      Aug 15, 2005: Danbury demolishes old courthouse (Devlin and Janick quoted); Aug 19,30, 2005: WestConn midtown parking; Aug 30, 2005: State college enrollment increases.
    - August 2005 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55224 (Box clippings_7, Folder 30)
      Aug 4, 2005: Footbal coach John Burrell; Aug 18, 2005: Nicole Corbin, women's soccer.
    - September 2005 Clippings (originals), 55223 (Box clippings_7, Folder 31-32)
      Sep 4, 10, 2005: WestConn to take in displaced students from Tulane and Loyola; Sep 6, 2005: Student Chris Hennessy's efforts to assist victims of Katrina; Sep 10, 2005: Prof. Anam Govardhan has close call with Katrina; concert to benefit Katrina victims; Sep 17, 2005: Bill Clinton coming to town; Sep 27, 2005: Dedication of science building; Sep 30, 2005: Magnet school first year plan.
    - September 2005 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55222 (Box clippings_7, Folder 33)
      Sep 1-2, 2005: Ashley Griffin, women's soccer goalkeeper; Sep 3, 2005: Joe DiMeglio, senior quarterback; Sep 4,7, 2005: Nicole Corbin, women's soccer all-time leading scorer; Sep 5, 2005: Vinny Cosentino, NJAC special teams player of the week.
    - October 2005 Clippings (originals), 55221 (Box clippings_7, Folder 34)
      Oct 3-4,9, 2005: Former Pres. Clinton returns to thank students for tsunami relief effort; Oct 14, 2005: Jim Pegolotti review: WestConn Symphonic Band; Oct 20, 2005: Northeast Generation ponders future of Candlewood, Lillinonah and Zoar (editorial); Oct 21, 2005: Forum to focus on rules for Candlewood Lake; Oct 22, 2005: Orianna DeMasi, WestConn student, visits Australia to aid endangered species; Oct 31, 2005: WestConn's rebuilt Steinway piano.
    - October 2005 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55220 (Box clippings_7, Folder 35)
      Oct 6, 2005: Matt Cusack men's soccer; Oct 9, 2005: Joe DiMeglio, quarterback; Oct 16, 2005: Jason Alcin and Adamis Gonzalez, football.
    - November 2005 Clippings (originals), 55219 (Box clippings_7, Folder 36-37)